{
    "id": "521e4b29e0e94cc794f775c55c31b0f7",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There are only ......................... apples on the tree.",
            "description": "Only a few means the same as few.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "less",
                "a few",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "49ff313a73ea4ccb87decf985539cd0e"
        },
        {
            "question": "There aren't .............................. apples on the tree.",
            "description": "We use many before a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "625cbbce84b34bcc8d6bf1a10c786e2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "We don't have ............................ time to finish the work.",
            "description": "We use much before an uncountable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "757dd7259b90473ba77231417141d60f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I collected ................................ money than my brother.",
            "description": "We use less before an uncountable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "few",
                "little",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "814e2224ec3c40ad9e37b4f739d717f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Now I have got ............................... problems than I used to have.",
            "description": "We use fewer before a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "fewer",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "54fda62bdef344bcb131c0b265f7cf4e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I solved the problem with ............................. difficulty.",
            "description": "We use little before an uncountable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "982a63f38be74370b57fa81ca8bde97e"
        },
        {
            "question": "There were ............................... people at the party.",
            "description": "We use few before a plural noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "little",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f8ea704434614b87bed56a7dc509f1c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is very ............................ sugar in the jar. We should buy some.",
            "description": "We use little before an uncountable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "less",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b58d9cac10e74fd3a53b35bd0e976e2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "There were ................................. students than expected.",
            "description": "We use fewer before a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "fewer",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5478878d8882439fb5f6fdf65035a884"
        },
        {
            "question": "I answered ................................ questions than you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "fewer",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3e317812e26b4517899a7583ceecd2a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................... politicians are really honest.",
            "description": "We use few before a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "Fewer",
                "Less"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1b4d514e3a48417bbd8f3c22c6836b79"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have .................................. interest in politics.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "little",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6f8c21e7158941dcae5e135bafa222a8"
        }
    ]
}